tonightsgirlfriend.com 2013-06-30

# Privacy Policy

**LA TOURAINE, INC. WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

Effective Date: August 9th, 2011

**I.INTRODUCTION**

A.La Touraine, Inc. ("us," "we," or "Company") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its members, visitors, and all users of tonightsgirlfriend.com (the "Site"). We created this La Touraine, Inc. Website Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and protection of your privacy. The Privacy Policy will explain the information we routinely collect during the operation of the Site and how we utilize it to maximize your experience.

B.The Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, or use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. Your selection of an ad banner or link may redirect you from the Site to a third party website. Company has no control over and no liability for any third party websites, materials, or for the privacy practices of any such third party website. You should direct any concerns regarding any external link to the third party site's administrator or webmaster.

C.Company's Site contains sexually explicit material and is not intended to be viewed by anyone under the age of 18 or who has not reached the age of majority in their community. Membership and access to the Site are expressly and strictly limited to adults at least 18 years of age who have reached the age of majority in their community.

**II.INFORMATION COLLECTION POLICY**

A.TRAFFIC DATA COLLECTED.

1)In order to collect certain information, we utilize small pieces of data that are placed on a user's computer when the user visits the Site ("Cookies"). Some Cookies are stored in a user's web browser and become inactive when the user closes his/her web browser or turns off his/her computer ("Session Cookies"). Other Cookies are longer lasting and reside on a user's hard drive ("Persistent Cookies"). Persistent Cookies remain on a user's computer until the Persistent Cookies expire or are manually deleted. Persistent Cookies may contain email addresses or usernames, but that data is encrypted and can only be interpreted by Company.

2)We use Cookies to recognize you when you return to the Site, which allows for easier login, customization of your experience, and overall Site efficiency. We also set Cookies for various tracking and user profiling purposes, such as identifying the pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct while on the Site. Additionally, we use cookies to track sales and to facilitate payout agreements with our affiliates when appropriate.

3)In the administration of the Site, we use third party software solutions such as NATS and Google Analytics which also utilize Cookies ("Third Party Cookies"). Through the use of internal methods and the use of Third Party Cookies, we automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit the Site: (a) your IP address (which allows us to determine your geographic location); (b) domain servers; (c) type of computer used to access the Site; and (d) type of web browser used to access the Site (collectively "Traffic Data").

4)Google Analytics has access to the information collected by the Third Party Cookies contained in their software; however, that data is anonymous. With that exception, at this time, we do not share information collected by Cookies with third parties.

5)Most web browsers allow a user to disable Cookies. While allowing Cookies is not a requirement for membership or use of the Site, if you elect to disable Cookies, some of the Site features will not function properly as the Site was not designed to operate without Cookies.

B.PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED.

1)In order to become a member of the Site (a "Member"), and/or to purchase products offered through the Site, you are required to provide certain information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") to one of our transaction processors (the "Processing Agent").

2)Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (a) your name and email address ("Contact Data"); (b) your zip code ("Demographic Data"); and (c) your credit card, telephone, or account number ("Financial Data"). The Processing Agent provides us with your Contact Data and Demographic Data, which we store. The Processing Agent does not provide us access to your Financial Data and therefore we have no ability to collect, store, or transfer that information.

3)If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. Please be aware that any information that you disclose in chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups is available to the public. Please take note that you should exercise caution when deciding to publicly disclose any Personal Information.

**III.INFORMATION USE POLICY**

A.COMPANY USE OF INFORMATION.

1)Company and Processing Agent use Contact Data to provide account status, to provide promotional materials and updates on our products and services, and to contact the user when necessary.

2)The Processing Agent uses your Financial Data to verify your qualifications for certain products or services and to bill you for such products and services when appropriate.

3)Company uses your Personal Information and Traffic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Site, displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences.

4)Company uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad Traffic Data information as described in II.A. above.

B.SHARING PERSONAL INFORMATION.

1)We share certain categories of information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We share Demographic Data with advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate basis whereby you are not personally identifiable. We share Contact Data with other companies who may want to send you information about their products or services, unless you have specifically requested that we not share Contact Data with such companies. We also share Contact Data and Financial Data with our business associates, including the Processing Agent, who assist us by performing core services including without limitation hosting, billing, transaction processing, fulfillment, or data storage and security related to the operation of the Site.

2)If you do not want us to share your Contact Data with any third parties, please email us at [policies@tonightsgirlfriend.com](mailto:policies@tonightsgirlfriend.com) or select the "opt-out" box on our online forms, but please understand that such a request will likely limit your ability to take advantage of all of the features and services we offer on the Site.

C.USER CHOICE REGARDING COLLECTION, USE, AND DISTRIBUTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use the Site; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Site that require your Personal Information. If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from us or from some of our business associates, you may select the appropriate "opt-out" option each time we ask you for Personal Information.

**IV.CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

A.SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (1) comply with a court order or other legal process; (2) protect our rights or property; or (3) enforce our Terms of Service. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit your Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser.

B.USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION.

Unfortunately, Company does not maintain any procedures for you to review or request changes to the information that we or Agent collect about you, except that you may request that we remove all information about you from our database by contacting as described below.

C.LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION.

You must promptly notify us if your credit card, user name, or password is lost, stolen, or used without your permission through the procedure provided in the [Terms of Service](http://www.tonightsgirlfriend.com/terms-of-service.html).

**V.UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. Specifically, in the event that Company elects to share Cookies information in the future, you will be notified via an update to this Privacy Policy or notice posted to the Site and at that time have the option to cease using the Site and/or terminate your membership. Your continued use of the Site after receiving such notice indicates your agreement to the sharing of Cookies information.

All membership questions can be answered by submitting a ticket to: [http://support.tonightsgirlfriend.com](http://support.tonightsgirlfriend.com/).

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our practices related to this Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database, please feel free to contact us at the following email address: [policies@tonightsgirlfriend.com](mailto:policies@tonightsgirlfriend.com) .
